{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4372","name":"Motor City Casino-Lodge Diner","address":"2901 Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Motor City Casino","licenseNumber":"072861","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.06763,42.33944","geojson":{"id":"4372","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.067633488,42.3394391140001]},"properties":{"name":"Motor City Casino-Lodge Diner","owner":"Motor City Casino","address":"2901 Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"072861","establishmentid":"4372","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/13/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4951","name":"Det. Delta Prep. Acad for Social Justice","address":"3550 John C Lodge","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1563","name":"Detroit Rescue Mission","address":"3535 Third St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"805","name":"Nancy Whiskey ","address":"2644 Harrison","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"436","name":"Jumbo's Bar","address":"3736 Third St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1865","name":"Detroit Housing Commission","address":"1231 Selden, Bldg 503","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3598","name":"Cass Technical High School","address":"2501 Second Ave","zipcode":"48201-34"},{"establishmentid":"4938","name":"UFO Factory","address":"2110 Trumbull St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2015","name":"Motor City Coney & Grill","address":"3641 Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"5359","name":"Detroit Shipping Company- Bars","address":"474 Peterboro St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622714","name":"-320 Coffee & Creamery","address":"474 Peterboro Street #201","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622644","name":"Coop","address":"474 Peterboro St #104","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622705","name":"Brujo","address":"474 Peterboro St #105","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622643","name":"Bangkok 96","address":"474 Peterboro Street #103","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"500","name":"McShane's","address":"1460 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"1140","name":"Masonic Temple","address":"500 Temple","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4648","name":"Ottava Via","address":"1400 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622606","name":"Founders Brewing Company","address":"456 Charlotte St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"545","name":"Nemos","address":"1378 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622463","name":"Corktown Tavern Inc.","address":"1716 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4781","name":"Bucharest Grill","address":"1623 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43726","inspectionDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Raw ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 180 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41827","inspectionDate":"2018-04-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"Food","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Cabinet(s) (lower)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Cookline","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the Wall (front)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"38173","inspectionDate":"2017-03-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Grease collection device","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the top of  Ice machine","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"36399","inspectionDate":"2016-09-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4372"}}